

Erlend Brodal

Game Developer

I am a technical artist, currently living in Copenhagen- My specialties are shader development, procedural generation, and 3D. I have experience in creating custom tools for artist for software such as Unreal Engine and Unity. I mostly work with 3D Environments, both big and small, while organizing the whole art pipeline from Sketch to Build.

Work Experience

Technical Art Director at Sharp Raccoon, Trondheim

AUGUST 2020 - NOW

Co-founder of the company, working as the lead Artist My contribution is developing the workflow and pipeline for modelling and shaders

Software Developer at Way AS, Trondheim

JUNE 2019 – 2020

Working on a Car Simulator

Education

Master's in games, IT-University of Copenhagen

AUGUST 2020 - NOW

Bachelor' in Games and Entertainment Technology, Nord University

JUNE 2016 - 2019



www.erlendbrodal.com







SKILLS

Animation

3D Modeling

Shaders

Texturing

Terrain

UI

Design

















